<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Academic Satire | Prof Y Not's Comedy Books</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/</link><description>Discover hilarious satire books by Academic Satire. Academic comedy, witty humor, and laugh-out-loud reads available on Amazon Kindle and paperback.</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:12:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://academicsatire.com/tags/professor-jokes/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>10 Signs You've Spent Too Long in Academia (A Satirist's Guide)</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/10-signs-spent-too-long-academia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/10-signs-spent-too-long-academia/</guid><description>You know you&amp;rsquo;ve spent too long in academia when the phrase &amp;ldquo;let&amp;rsquo;s table this discussion&amp;rdquo; fills you with both rage and resignation. Here are ten signs that the ivory tower has become less of a workplace and more of a lifestyle.
1. You Have Opinions About Fonts Not just &amp;ldquo;Comic Sans is unprofessional&amp;rdquo; opinions. We&amp;rsquo;re talking &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t take this email seriously because they used Calibri instead of Times New Roman, and everyone knows Calibri is for people who&amp;rsquo;ve given up&amp;rdquo; opinions.</description><enclosure url="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1481627834876-b7833e8f5570?w=1200&amp;q=80" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Analysis Paralysis: Why Picking Dinner Ruins Your Life</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-exhausted-by-decisions-that-dont-matter-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-exhausted-by-decisions-that-dont-matter-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Decision Fatigue &amp;amp; Overthinking and why How To Be Exhausted By Decisions That Don&amp;rsquo;t Matter is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/9179uhuLOFL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Barber Shop Anxiety: Dodging Sausages and Small Talk</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-dodge-the-barbers-sausage-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-dodge-the-barbers-sausage-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Awkward Encounters and why HOW TO DODGE THE BARBER’S SAUSAGE WHILE GETTING A HAIRCUT is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81aaZf3oKWL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Broke but Confident: How to Survive Inflation with Swag</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-broke-with-confidence-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-broke-with-confidence-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Financial Satire and why How To Be Broke With Confidence is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91q6nJuywkL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Dating Nightmares: Holding in Farts and Other Rom-Com Lies</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-hold-in-your-fart-when-talking-to-your-crush-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-hold-in-your-fart-when-talking-to-your-crush-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Dating Disasters and why How To Hold In Your Fart When Talking To Your Crush is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81z4n4qYxQL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Energy Saving Mode: Why Laziness is Just Efficiency in Disguise</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/im-not-lazy-im-on-energy-saving-mode-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/im-not-lazy-im-on-energy-saving-mode-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Productivity Satire and why I&amp;rsquo;m Not Lazy I&amp;rsquo;m On Energy Saving Mode is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91XlR1IxWAL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Facing Your Problems When the Problem is Your Face</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-can-you-face-your-problem-when-the-problem-is-your-face-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-can-you-face-your-problem-when-the-problem-is-your-face-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Self-Esteem Satire and why How Can You Face Your Problem When the Problem Is Your Face ? is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71NDLPEIUCL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Faking Success: How to Wing It Until You Make It</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/i-have-no-idea-what-i-am-doing-but-its-working-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/i-have-no-idea-what-i-am-doing-but-its-working-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Faking Success and why I Have No Idea What I am Doing But It&amp;rsquo;s Working is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91mdheGdhSL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>Fitness Satire: Why I Want to Donate My Body Fat</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-can-i-double-my-body-fat-and-give-it-to-the-next-person-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-can-i-double-my-body-fat-and-give-it-to-the-next-person-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Diet &amp;amp; Fitness Satire and why How Can I Double My Body Fat And Give It To The Next Person is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/711nFogc2pL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How Can I Double My Body Fat And Give It To The Next Person</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-can-i-double-my-body-fat-and-give-it-to-the-next-person/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-can-i-double-my-body-fat-and-give-it-to-the-next-person/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? A wildly absurd, laugh-out-loud collection of satirical stories that poke fun at self-help culture and miracle fitness hacks.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How Can I Double My Body Fat And Give It To The Next Person comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/711nFogc2pL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How Can You Face Your Problem When the Problem Is Your Face ?</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-can-you-face-your-problem-when-the-problem-is-your-face/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-can-you-face-your-problem-when-the-problem-is-your-face/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? A hilarious collection of satire and painfully relatable stories about the everyday disasters we all pretend we’re too mature to still experience.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How Can You Face Your Problem When the Problem Is Your Face ? comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71NDLPEIUCL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Achieve Burnout Without Achieving Anything</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-achieve-burnout-without-achieving-anything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-achieve-burnout-without-achieving-anything/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Tired of &amp;lsquo;rising and grinding&amp;rsquo; toward a nervous breakdown? Stop accidentally succeeding and learn to fail with intention.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Achieve Burnout Without Achieving Anything comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91WigqKWRqL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Be Broke With Confidence</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-broke-with-confidence/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-broke-with-confidence/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Ever wondered how to stay broke forever—and somehow feel amazing about it? The ultimate satire self-help book for financial disasters.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Be Broke With Confidence comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91q6nJuywkL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Be Exhausted By Decisions That Don't Matter</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-exhausted-by-decisions-that-dont-matter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-exhausted-by-decisions-that-dont-matter/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Paralyzed by what brand of toothpaste to buy? Exhausted by the 4:00 PM &amp;lsquo;what&amp;rsquo;s for dinner&amp;rsquo; crisis? Finally, a parody self-help guide that understands your struggle.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Be Exhausted By Decisions That Don&amp;rsquo;t Matter comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/9179uhuLOFL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Be Late Even When You Start Early</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-late-even-when-you-start-early/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-late-even-when-you-start-early/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Ever started getting ready two hours early only to end up ten minutes late? Welcome to the definitive parody self-help guide for the chronically late.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Be Late Even When You Start Early comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91HiLxrp-XL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Be Productive Without Producing Anything</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-productive-without-producing-anything/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-be-productive-without-producing-anything/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Tired of working nonstop and still getting nothing done? A sharp productivity satire that exposes the art of fake productivity.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Be Productive Without Producing Anything comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91o3z8RJ5TL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>HOW TO DODGE THE BARBER’S SAUSAGE WHILE GETTING A HAIRCUT</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-dodge-the-barbers-sausage/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-dodge-the-barbers-sausage/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? A wild ride through the treacherous world of barber chairs and rogue sausages. A tongue-in-cheek survival manual for awkward trims.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, HOW TO DODGE THE BARBER’S SAUSAGE WHILE GETTING A HAIRCUT comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81aaZf3oKWL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Fart And Blame It On Someone: A Gaslighting Guide</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-fart-and-blame-it-on-someone/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-fart-and-blame-it-on-someone/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? Ever been caught in a suspiciously smelly situation? This groundbreaking guide will teach you the ancient art of flatulent misdirection.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Fart And Blame It On Someone: A Gaslighting Guide comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81SeN2VjMIL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How To Hold In Your Fart When Talking To Your Crush</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-hold-in-your-fart-when-talking-to-your-crush/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/books/how-to-hold-in-your-fart-when-talking-to-your-crush/</guid><description>Are You Ready to Laugh at Your Own Misery? A hilarious collection of awkward, relatable, and absolutely ridiculous stories about the moments we all pretend never happened.
In a world obsessed with perfection, high achievement, and maintaining a curated Instagram feed, How To Hold In Your Fart When Talking To Your Crush comes as a breath of fresh air (or a sigh of relief). This isn&amp;rsquo;t just a book; it&amp;rsquo;s a mirror reflecting the hilarity of our modern struggles.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81z4n4qYxQL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item><item><title>How to Look Busy at Work Without Doing Anything</title><link>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-productive-without-producing-anything-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://academicsatire.com/blog/how-to-be-productive-without-producing-anything-blog/</guid><description>We explore the hilarious reality of Fake Productivity and why How To Be Productive Without Producing Anything is the manual you need right now.</description><enclosure url="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91o3z8RJ5TL._SL1500_.jpg" type="image/jpeg"/></item></channel></rss>